moderncat.net 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy • hauspanther

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit our website.

### PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on our site, we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here.](https://automattic.com/privacy/) After approval of your comment, your Gravatar profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### WHO WE SHARE YOUR DATA WITH

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our readers use our site and to better serve our readers. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

For more information on the privacy policies of websites and services we use:

### HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR DATA

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

### WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE OVER YOUR DATA

If you have left comments on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

If you have questions about our privacy policy, or if you would like to register a complaint, please contact us via email at [info@hauspanther.com](mailto:info@hauspanther.com) or by mail at 530 E McDowell Rd. #107-433, Phoenix, AZ 85004, USA.
